

#### CONTACT

- +66612269670
- developer.maythinn@gmail.com
- Pangkok, Thailand
- in may-thinn-khine

#### LANGUAGE

English

Myanmar

## **MAY THINN KHINE**

## Senior Frontend Developer

#### ABOUT ME

I am a Senior Frontend Developer with 8 years experience in building websites using React js, Next js and MUI. And also a founder of <u>MT Coding - Tech</u>. Let's collaborate and create exceptional digital experiences together. This is <u>my portfolio</u>.

#### EDUCATION

# Yangon University of Distance Education (2010 - 2013)

Bachelor of Arts (English)

#### Fairway Technology (2019)

Certified Rockstar Developer Course

 ES6, Node JS, Express JS, React, React Native, Redux

#### Fairway Technology (2018)

Certified Software Engineering Fundamental Course

 Computational Thinking, Data Structure, Basic Algorithms, OOP, DOM APIs

#### **Brighter Myanmar (2017)**

**Certified Professional Web development class** 

· HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap

#### SKILLS

- React JS
- Next JS
- Material UI (MUI)
- Token Base UI (Design Tokens)
- PWA
- Redux
- Redux-saga
- Git
- styled-components
- Vue
- Vuetify
- Nuxt JS
- HTML
- CSS
- SASS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- Bootstrap and other...

#### EXPERIENCE

## 1. ONOW Myanmar

(2022 - 2024)

Senior Frontend Developer

I have taken the frontend lead on

- PWA Product (React, Next, MUI, Redux, Redux-Saga, PWA, Axios, API binding, Git)
- CMS Product (React, Next, MUI, Redux, Redux-Saga, Redux-toolkit, Axios, API binding, Design Tokens, Git)
- Design System with Design Tokens (React, Next, Style-Dictionary, MUI)

leveraging my expertise to drive their successful execution and delivery.

• CRM Web App(React, Next, Style-Dictionary, MUI, PWA).

#### 2. MT Coding - Tech

(2021 - Present)

Founder/Instructor

- As the founder and lead instructor of MT Coding Tech, I have had the privilege of guiding numerous students through our programs. The positive feedback received from these students underscores the effectiveness of our teaching methods and the value of the education they receive.
- Here is students review <a href="https://lnkd.in/gS3m6ysN">https://lnkd.in/gS3m6ysN</a>
- Taught basic website design principles, focusing on HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Provided personalized feedback to foster student growth.
- Led students through constructing three diverse web projects.
  - 1. https://developer-maythinn.github.io/bootstrap-template/
  - 2. https://developer-maythinn.github.io/simple-html-scsstemplate/
  - 3.netflix clone

#### 3. Myanmar Youth Initiative

(2023)

Mentor

Mentoring for the participants about Web Development.

## 4. IM Ringier Co., Ltd (Duwun Media)

(2019 - 2022)

Senior Frontend Developer

- I advanced from the position of Web Designer to Senior Frontend Developer.
  Throughout this period, I played a pivotal role in the development of a production-level website.
- Work interchangeably with their advertising, editorial, and marketing teams to drive their company's exponential growth.
- https://www.duwun.com.mm (React, Next, MUI, Redux, Redux-Saga, Axios, API binding, Git)

## 5. IM Ringier Co., Ltd (Duwun Media)

(2017 - 2019)

Web Designer

• I played a pivotal role in the the beta version of a Progressive Web App (PWA) using with **Vue JS**, **Vuetify**, **Nuxt JS**, **PWA**.

#### 6. 72Coder Software Co.,Ltd

(2016 - 2017)

Web Developer

- · Working with the development team.
- Building web design for three projects.
  - Hospital Website
  - NGO Web Page
  - Mobile Phone Shop Website(For Internship)